<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asif Mammadov's Personal Page</title><link>https://asifmv.com/</link><description>Recent content on Asif Mammadov's Personal Page</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2022</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:05:20 +0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://asifmv.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using Traefik as a reverse proxy</title><link>https://asifmv.com/blog/traefik-as-reverse-proxy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:05:20 +0400</pubDate><guid>https://asifmv.com/blog/traefik-as-reverse-proxy/</guid><description>A reverse proxy is a server that acts as an intermediary between a client and one or more servers. It can help with load balancing, SSL termination, caching, and many other tasks. One of the most popular tools for setting up a reverse proxy is Traefik. It has a rich set of features, is fast to configure, and is highly flexible for custom functionality and integration. This post will follow the steps to set up a reverse proxy using Traefik.</description></item><item><title>Setting Up Self-Signed Certificate on Windows</title><link>https://asifmv.com/blog/setting-up-self-signed-certificate-on-windows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 09:15:20 +0400</pubDate><guid>https://asifmv.com/blog/setting-up-self-signed-certificate-on-windows/</guid><description>Self-signed certificates are public key certificates used in testing environments. They are not issued by Certificate Authority (CA) and thus do not provide any trust. Yet they are free and easy to create, which is an excellent option for testing applications with endpoints over HTTPS.
There are several ways to create a certificate on Windows: OpenSSL, makecert, Windows Certificate Manager (Certmgr), and Powershell&amp;rsquo;s New-SelfSignedCertificate cmdlet. I will use the latter in this post as it is built-in in Powershell and utilizes CLI.</description></item><item><title>CV</title><link>https://asifmv.com/cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://asifmv.com/cv/</guid><description>Experience # Software Engineer 2022-08 - present Simbrella — Mobile Fintech Services Baku, Azerbaijan Fintech company that developes financial services for Financial Institutions, Mobile Wallets and MNOs to offer loans to massive segments of untapped customers. We provide digital and instant financial services and reduce cost of risk applying AI-based models to efficiently assess customers’ creditworthiness.
Main contributor to development of internal End-to-End testing framework that reduced amount of deployment incidents and bugs by 80% saving over 40 thousands of dollars per quarter.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://asifmv.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://asifmv.com/projects/</guid><description>Team lead, Developer 2022-04 - 2022-02 Music2Notes (application) — Web app that transcribes songs to sheet music. Python, Librosa, Flask, React.js Team lead, Developer 2021-04 - 2021-06 Codenames Online (application) — Team Lead and Developer of the popular multiplayer board game with live rooms, chat system, and leaderboard. Express.js, React.js, Socket.io, CI/CD, Heroku Developer 2021-05 - 2021-06 Conway&amp;#39;s Game of Life (application) — CLI and GUI (with SDL) for the evolutionary cellular automation devised by Mr.</description></item></channel></rss>